Guide to Boston University Catalogs, etc. Cubb.00214
Cubberley Education Library
Boston University
1869-1977
Cubberley Education Library
Cubb.00214
406 item(s) Yearbooks for 1882-1884, 1887-1912/13, 1915/16-1925/26 Catalogs for 1927/28-1963/65
Located in Boston, Mass. Established in 1839 in Newbury, Vermont as the Methodist General Biblical Institute. Moved to Boston in 1867 and became Boston Theological Serminary. Was chartered and changed name to Boston University in 1869.
Massachusetts
- Boston University: College of Liberal Arts, 1898-1962; 27 item(s) Catalogs for 1898/99, 1911/12, 1915/16, 1921/22, 1924/25-1928/29, 1933/34-1935/36, 1937/38-1947/48, 1951/52-1952/53, 1956/57-1957/58, 1960/62
- Boston University: Revised Requirements for Admission and Degrees in the College of Liberal Arts, July 1917; 1 item(s) Bulletin for July 1917
- Boston University: School of Medicine, 1905-1975; 39 item(s) Catalogs for 1905, 1907, 1914-1916, 1921/22-1922/23, 1924/25, 1927/28-1928/29, 1930-1932, 1934-1942/43, 1944/45-1945/46, 1947/48-1953/54, 1955/56-1957/58, 1959/60-1962/63, 1964/66, 1974/75
  Medical colleges
- Boston University: President's Annual Report, 1874-1966; 48 item(s) Reports for 1874/75-1894, 1896-1898, 1900-1903, 1905, 1907, 1909-1911, 1915-1916, 1918-1925, 1942, 1944, 1946, 1948-1950, 1959, 1964/65-1965/66
- Boston University: Annual Reports of the President and Treasurer of the University, 1925-1955; 20 item(s) Reports for 1925/26-1928, 1930-1934, 1936-1941, 1943, 1951- 1954/55
- Boston University: The Treasurer's Annual Report, 1954-1963; 4 item(s) Reports for 1954-1956, 1963
- Boston University: Historical Register, 1869-1891, 1 item(s) Bound with President's Annual Report
- Boston University: Graduate School, 1922-1970; 23 item(s) Announcements for 1922/23, 1927/28-1928/29, 1930/31-1932/33, 1936/37-1938/39, 1944/45, 1946/47-1948/49, 1950/51, 1952/53, 1955/56-1957/58, 1960/62-1962/63, 1965/67-1968/70
- Boston University: School of Law, 1908-1973; 41 item(s) Bulletins for 1908-1908/09, 1921-1956/57, 1958/59, 1960/62-1962/64, 1967/69, 1972/73
  Law schools
  - Boston University: School of Law Graduate Tax Program, 1962-1963; 1 item(s) Bulletin for 1962/63
- Boston University: Summer Term, 1915-1967; 41 item(s) Catalogs for 1915, 1919-1920, 1922, 1924, 1928-1930, 1933-1949, 1953, 1954, 1956-1959, 1963, 1965 Business Administration & Commercial Subjects 1919 Preliminary Announcement 1941, 1947-1948, 1950-1952, 1955, 1958
- Boston University: College of Business Administration, 1918-1968; 15 item(s) Catalogs for 1944/45-1945/46, 1947/48, 1949/50-1953/54, 1955/56, 1957/58-1961/63 Bulletin for Day and Evening Course for 1918/19
  Business schools
- Boston University: College of Practical Arts and Letters, 1928; 1 item(s) Bulletin for 1928
- Boston University: School of Religious Education and Social Service, 1920-1929; 5 item(s) Catalogs for 1920/21-1923/24, 1928/29
  - Boston University: Standardizing Religious Education as a New Profession, [1926]; 1 item(s) Pamphlet rec'd March 1926
- Boston University: School of Religious and Social Work, 1937-1939; 8 item(s) Catalogs for 1937-1939
  - Boston University: School of Religion and Social Work, Division of Social Work, 1938-1941; 5 item(s) Graduate Announcement 1938/39 Announcement 1939/40-1940/41
    - Social Work as a Career, 1939-1940; 1 item(s) Flyer from the Division of Social Work
    - Boston University: Deering Community Center Summer School, 1939; 1 item(s) Brochure for 1939
- Boston University: School of Education, 1937-1977; 10 item(s) Catalogs for 1937/38, 1940/41-1941/42, 1944/45, 1952/53, 1956/57-1957/58, 1960/62, 1965/67, 1976/77
- Boston University: School of Social Work, 1941-1975; 11 item(s) Catalogs for 1941/42-1944/45, 1954/55-1957/58, 1967/69, 1974/75
- Boston University: School of Public Relations, 1947-1950; 3 item(s) Catalogs for 1947/48-1949/50
- Boston University: School of Public Relations and Communications, 1951-1962; 7 item(s) Catalogs for 1951/52, 1955/56-1960/62
- Boston University: School of Nursing, 1953-1965; 3 item(s) Catalogs for 1953/54, 1957/58, 1963/65
  Nursing schools
- Boston University: College of General Education, 1957-1960; 2 item(s) Catalog for 1957/58, 1959/60
- Boston University: Sargent College of Physical Education, 1957-1958; 1 item(s) Catalog for 1957/58
- Boston University: Sargent College of Allied Health Professions, 1971-1972; 1 item(s) Catalog for 1971/72
- Boston University: College of Industrial Technology, 1954-1958; 2 item(s) Catalogs for 1954/56, 1957/58
- Boston University: Junior College, 1953-1958; 2 item(s) Catalogs for 1953/54, 1957/58
- Boston University: School of Fine and Applied Arts, 1957-1962; 3 item(s) Catalogs for 1957/58-1958/59, 1960/62
- Boston University: Undergraduate Study, 1966-1977; 7 item(s) Catalogs for 1966, 1967/68-1969/70, 1972/73, 1975/76-1976/77
- Boston University Bulletin, April 18, 1933; 1 item(s) General introduction to Boston University in 1933
- Boston University: General Information Bulletin, 1957-1958; 1 item(s) Catalog for 1957/58
- Boston University Facts, [1977]; 1 item(s) An introduction to Boston University rec'd June 1977.
- Boston University: School of Management Issue Graduate Programs, 1976-1977; 1 item(s) Catalog for 1976/77